kensavage.com 2009-12-27

# Privacy Policy

## January 14, 2008

## Privacy Policy

KenSavage.com respects your right to privacy. This statement discloses the privacy practices for the KenSavage.com website. This statement also describes other important topics relating to your privacy.

### Personal information

At KenSavage.com, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit KenSavage.com on the Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may request information from you, such as your name, address, title, company name, telephone number, or email address, that you voluntarily provide. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you on the Internet. If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet — to correspond with you, process a request for return contact, or to provide you with further information, for example — it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, and then we discard it.

### Information security and quality

We intend to protect the integrity of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and managerial procedures to maintain information that is accurate, current, and complete. We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. We will make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to correct personal information inaccuracies in a timely manner. You always have the right to access the information we have about you.

Some of our Web pages may contain “cookies,” which are data that may be sent to your web browser and stored on your computer. This allows our server to recognize you when you visit our Web site in the future and allows KenSavage.com the capability to improve our website and better meet your needs. Most web browsers can be configured to not accept cookies, or to notify you if a cookie is sent to you.

We use Google Analytics, which is covered by [Google’s Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html).

### Business relationships

The KenSavage.com site may contain links to other websites, including those of our business partners. KenSavage.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

### Email

If KenSavage.com sends you an email for which you have opted-in by voluntarily providing KenSavage.com with personally identifiable information, there will be a link on the page that allows you to “unsubscribe” to any additional emails by typing in the word “unsubscribe” in the subject line and replying. KenSavage.com will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally suppress you from our database.

### Retention of information

If you have submitted personal information to KenSavage.com electronically and would like it removed or modified, please contact us by sending an email using the form below. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to comply with your request.

### Right to modify

KenSavage.com reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. KenSavage.com will promptly reflect any such modifications in these web pages.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should email us by using this form:

[privacy](http://www.kensavage.com/contact-ken-savage/privacy-policy/ "privacy") (1)
